Oh yeah.
At the beginning of the 21st
century, the Umbrella Corporation
had become the largest
commercial entity in the United States.
Nine out of every ten
homes contain its products.
Its political and financial
influences felt everywhere.
In public, it is the
world's leading supplier of
computer technology, medical
products, and healthcare.
Unknown even to its own employees,
its massive profits are generated
by military technology, genetic
experimentation, and viral weaponry.
Thank you.
Yeah.
It's not the only way I do.
What's that?
Hi, Drow.
Shit!
Hey, what the hell is going on?
You're gonna cover!
Open!
I'm trying!
Hey, grab it!
Move it out!
Shouldn't be, uh...
Doors open or something?
It's supposed to take
us to a nearest floor.
Hello?
What's up?
Mind's dead.
What's the problem?
The door's all open.
What about the ones at the back?
Not as well.
There's no fire here!
No fire!
There's no fire!
We have to get out of here.
Take it easy.
You take it easy.
Quiet.
What is that?
Oh my god.
Oh.
You have to get out of here.
We have to get out of this building.
Here, give me a hand.
But, okay.
I need some bars, they'll go.
They're caught on something.
That's why they're not.
I can squeeze through.
Okay, help.
Oh.
That's that.
You gotta have a touch.
That's it.
A bit more.
Pull this out.
It's the brakes!
Click it out!
Put your head out of the way!
Yeah!
you
Hello?
Oh, touch me!
So good.
I know what you're talking about.
So, the housing primary
defenses have been activated.
She's probably still
suffering inside effect.
What about the cop?
I met you, Edison.
I'm not getting the match.
Who are you?
I'm Jack Srayford.
They probably don't
even have me on file yet.
The local's on efficient.
It's possible.
Should I sit here and hear?
You can't do this!
Hey!
Prep for entry to the hive.
Power's down.
So fix it.
I'm on it.
Jumping.
And clear.
He had a problem.
How's that door?
Sealed shit.
Let me.
Jumping?
Why still?
Watch this light.
Far away.
I don't know.
He's fine.
Memory loss.
Just like the other one.
No.
You and I have the same employer.
We all work for the umbrella corporation.
The mansion above us is an
emergency entrance to the hive.
You are security operatives,
placed there to protect that entrance.
What about this?
Your marriage is a fake.
Just part of your cover to
protect the secrecy of the hive.
And what is the hive?
Children.
Accessing schematic of the hive.
The high itself is located underground.
Deep beneath the streets of Raccoon City.
top secret research facility owned
and operated by the umbrella operation.
The hive houses over 500 technicians
and scientists that support them.
They live and work underground.
Their research is of
the highest importance.
Its nature is classified.
Our position on the map is
indicated by heat signature.
Why can't I remember anything?
The hive has its own defense mechanisms.
All computer control.
A nerve gas was released into the house.
Primary effective the gas complete
unconsciousness lasted in, up to four hours.
Secondary effects are varied
but can include acute memory loss.
For how long?
Subject to an hour, date, week.
So you're saying this place was attacked?
I'm afraid things aren't a little
more complicated than that.
Sir, we've reached the high.
We all come down, it's dissipated.
Makes it easier to work
underground, thinking there's a deal.
Looks like we're taking the stairs.
This is going to slow us down.
Our route to the Queen takes
us straight through these labs.
Brain, JD, see how bad the flooding is.
Doplin, find us an alternate route.
What happened to you?
Five hours ago, Rick, we went homicide.
See you behind until everyone down here.
Jesus.
When we realized what was happening,
my team was dispatched to shut her down.
Why did she do it?
But outside interference is a possibility.
Jesus.
Hey.
Okay.
Yeah.
And now it was...
Please, come on.
It's called me.
I... Do you remember anything?
I don't remember all of this.
No.
Nothing before the train.
Nothing.
Sir, no go, the whole level is flooded.
All right, we're behind schedule.
So let's move in.
Come on.
Poor bastards.
Thank you.
Dining hold B.
That's what it says on the map.
Maybe you're eating it wrong.
Maybe the corporation's
keeping a few secrets down here.
Something you're not supposed to see.
Jamie, you will reindeer the
prisoner here and secure the exit.
Sir, hey, on level, it's a
non-existent to this room.
You can be the system malfunctioned.
All right, and maybe it's a Bible.
You can be a search line to keep it tight.
I said, keep it tight.
Sorry.
I'm not sure I want to remember
what went on down here.
I don't blame you.
What the hell they keep at these things?
What's taking so long?
Drag Queen's defenses are in place.
She's making it difficult.
Let's back it up.
I'd like to automate it.
Not in the worry about it.
Transfer room position.
Roger.
Running the bypass.
Checkmate.
Move it.
What is that?
It has one's going to shut the queen down.
delivers a massive electrical charge.
Stramble is the mainframe
and forces it to rebuild.
What's that?
There's something killing this man!
Where are you going?
Shit got it
Let's do it.
Do what?
We have to complete the mission.
There's no way I'm going down there.
Our defenses are down.
Deja vu, anyone?
Give me a hand with this
Don't listen to anything she
says she's a holographic
representation of the Red Queen.
You have to get out.
Modeled after the head
program was daughter.
Try to deceive us.
Confuse us.
I wouldn't advise this, disabling
me or salting us with primary power.
Anything to stop us with shutting me down.
I implore you.
Employer away.
Please.
Please?
You're all going to die down here.
Okay.
Paul's force of the circuit breaker to
shut down her mainframe for 30 seconds.
After that, if I don't have
her board, she can reboot.
They're late.
Come on in.
JT, we gotta survive her!
It's okay, we're here to help.
You seem to be in some space.
You're off the moon!
Get off the moon!
Baby, get off the moon
before I stab her in!
You okay?
She bit me, man.
She took a chokeling right out of me.
I'm going to stay down.
She's crazy.
A minute closer than I'll find her.
I mean it.
I shot it five times.
How was she still standing?
Bitch isn't standing now.
What was all the shooting?
We found a survivor.
And you shot him?
She was crazed.
She bit me.
She's gone.
Bullshit!
She's alright here, but she's gone!
Look, look at this.
It's alive.
It's not much.
Looks like it's coagulated.
Yeah.
It's not possible.
Why not?
Because blood doesn't do
that until after you're dead.
Can we go now?
We're not going anywhere until
the rest of the scene get here.
There's no one else coming.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Wait.
What?
Don't come any closer.
They're behind us.
Jesus.
Everywhere.
Nice.
They're everywhere.
Let's go!
I can help you get the virus.
I have access to security
code surveillance plans.
Thanks.
You waited?
Didn't know the code.
Shit!
Come on, man.
What's did this alone?
I'm fine!
One, two, go!
Aah!
Where are the bodies?
Where did they go?
What ever they are?
It's pretty obvious what they are.
Landcoats, badges, those
people used to walk here!
All the people working here are dead.
Well, that isn't stopping
them from walking around.
But where did they jump from?
Why didn't we see them on the way in?
When you cut the power, you
unlock the doors, you let them out.
We're never gonna make it to the surface.
You are a security operative.
Security operative.
Please do protect better.
Oh.
I'm going to kill you.
Please, sir.
Oh!
I can help you get the virus.
I have access to security codes,
surveillance plans, the looks.
But... but there's gonna be a price.
Name it.
Is she my sister?
Corporations like Umbrella think
they're above the law, but they're not.
There are hundreds of thousands of
us who think the same all over the world.
Some of us provide information.
Others give their support.
Some take more direct action.
Like you.
Dear friends, I've been
a little more thorough.
They were seen right through my false ID.
And all the red flags would have gone
off, Quantico, NSA, by cap, all the rest.
There's no way I could
have infiltrated the hive.
So you sent your sister?
We needed something concrete.
Anything to expose umbrella to the press.
Proof of the research that
was going on down here.
Kind of research.
The illegal gun.
Genetic.
Borrow.
My sister was going to smuggle
out a sample of the virus.
They were developing.
So how was she going
to make it out of here?
She had a contact.
Within the hive, someone I never met.
That access to security
covered surveillance.
Everything she needed.
Somebody didn't she make it?
Maybe she trusted the wrong person.
Maybe they sent her up.
Keep the virus for themselves.
Do you have any idea how much the tea
virus would be worth on the open market?
Let me go this.
Yeah.
Do someone.
Don't shoot.
Don't
What about this?
They're waiting out there, too.
That way?
It's a dead end.
There's no way out of the Queen's Chamber.
So we wait.
Someone doesn't hear from you.
They'll send back up or something.
Right?
What?
What's wrong?
We don't have much time.
You know, those last doors
we pass on the way in from
the mansion, they seal
shut and just under and out.
If we're not out of here, by
then, we're not getting out.
Why are you talking about it?
You can't just bury us alive down here.
Containing the incident
is the only feels safe
plan they had against
possible contamination.
I'm only telling us this now.
When we trapped half a
fucking mile underground.
We have to find a way out of this room.
What are you doing?
Where are you taking
most of turning her back on?
That is not a good idea.
She'll know a way out of here.
So we're in the way she's being treated.
I'm sure she's going to be
real happy to help herself.
It's so good for you talking
about, can you bypass it?
Yeah.
So do it.
All right, so to break this the same time.
If I hit the switch, she
won't be able to shut down.
She's going to fry.
Okay.
The initial charge must
have damaged her boards.
Ah, there you are.
Things I gather have gone after control.
Give me that fucking switch right now.
I'm gonna fry her ass.
I did warn you, do you, Ty?
Tell us what the hell
is going on down here.
Research and development.
What about the team virus?
The team virus was a
major medical grade street.
Although it clearly all type of sex.
Highly comfortable military applications.
Well, how does it explain
those things out there?
It brings the dead back to life.
Not fully.
The subjects have the
simplest of mates' functions.
Perhaps a little memory,
virtually no intelligence.
They are driven by the basis of impulses.
The most basic of needs.
Which is?
The need to feed.
How do you kill them?
Severing the top of the
spinal column or massive
trauma to the brain are
the most effective methods.
You mean shoot them in the head.
Why did you kill everybody down here?
The T-virus escaped into
the air conditioning system,
and an uncontrolled
pattern of infection began.
The virus is protein,
changing from liquid to airborne
to blood transmission,
depending on its environment.
It's almost impossible to kill.
I couldn't allow it to escape from high.
So, I took steps.
You must understand.
Those who become
infected, I can't let it be.
Well, we're not infected.
Just one bite, one scratch
from these creatures is sufficient.
And then, you become one of them.
A check of my systems indicates my main
drive circuit breaker has been disabled.
May I ask why?
Insurance.
We need a way out of here.
If you refuse to help at
any time we flip the switch.
Understand?
After you?
What the hell is this place?
The utility tunnels.
They're running to meet the
hive for water gas power lines.
We've been in here before.
Keep moving.
Going around in circles.
All this is the route
that you're here to get.
It's moving.
We have no choice, but to keep moving,
because those things are right behind us.
You got that?
Let's go!
Come on!
Quickly, everyone go by the pipe!
Well, stop!
Come on, there's a way off!
Right there!
Keep it back!
Come on!
Get over here!
There's too many of you!
Stop!
Trady?
Wayne?
What?
You have to do something like you lose.
Fine.
I said I'm fine.
You like that, don't you, huh?
Huh?
You like the real taste, don't you?
I like the taste of that.
She was right.
We're all gonna die down here.
No.
Getting out.
All of this.
U.K.
I can't focus!
That's lucky I want you to go
No.
Not leaving you, Kaplan.
Yes, you are.
No.
You can't kill all of them.
I'm not going anywhere.
I want you to go now.
Please.
Just do it.
Just do it now.
Release.
You're gonna have to work for your meal!
When I get out of here,
I think I'm going to get laid.
Yeah, might want to
clean up a little bit first.
I think there's one here.
I have a screen for the antivirus.
There's a cure.
What are you talking about?
The process can be reversed.
There's a cure!
You're gonna be okay!
I was beginning to worry.
This is where they kept the tea virus.
I don't even know all this.
Because I was gonna steal it.
I was your sister's content.
You betrayed her.
I don't know.
You caused all of them.
Don't remember the truth.
I can help you get the virus.
I have access to security
codes surveillance plans for us.
But there's gonna be a price.
Name it.
You have to guarantee me that
you will bring this corporation down.
Spent.
Spend?
We can still make it out of here.
Come with me.
We can have everything we've ever wanted.
Money's out there waiting.
You wouldn't believe how much.
Is that how you thought all my
dreams were going to come true?
Please, I wouldn't want to shoot you.
Might need the bullets.
Back off.
I won't take any part of this.
Okay, but you can't just
wash your hands of this.
We worked for the same company.
You knew what they did.
These chains stopped.
You really believe that people
like him will ever change anything.
No, nothing ever changes.
Where?
Where is?
They had nightmares.
It's on the train.
They found me.
Couldn't have been standing
more than three feet, probably.
I so nearly made it out.
I didn't realize that a bit of a computer
had defense systems outside the hive.
In our house.
I'm missing you already.
No!
Your boyfriend's a real asshole.
He shot the locking mechanism out.
I can't believe that son of a
bitch is gonna get away with this.
I don't think so.
I've been a bad, bad girl.
Oh.
What the fuck is that?
One of the highest early
experiments, produced by Jackson the
T-Vines directly into living
tissue, the results were unstable.
Now that it has fed on
fresh DNA, it will mutate.
Becoming a stronger, faster hunter.
Root.
If you know it was loose,
why didn't you warn us?
Because she was saving it.
First.
Wasn't that right?
I didn't think any of you
would make it this far.
Not without infection.
Why didn't you tell us
about the anti-virus?
This no matter infection, there's
no guarantee it would work.
But there's a chance.
Right?
I don't deal in chance.
No pressure, guys.
You require the four digit access codes.
I can give you the code, but first
you must do something for me.
What do you want?
One of your groupies infected,
I require her life for the code.
You have the virus.
It's right there on the platform.
Right there!
I'm sorry, but it's the risk I cannot take.
She's right.
She's the only way.
I can't even have to kill any.
No.
The other one is, we all die down here.
The last is where you post.
First it won't talk right now.
Do it, no.
Just do it.
Wait, please get up.
Do it!
Don't have lunch to sign up.
Please, Joyce.
Kill her.
Don't hunt now.
You know, you don't have any choice.
Don't do it.
Don't do it now.
Please.
Do it.
Kill her.
The beach wouldn't open
the door, so I hit the fryer.
you
Start it up.
God!
I'm missing you already.
I can't believe there's nothing.
Come on, pal!
I don't want to be one of those things.
I'm looking around with that result.
When the time comes,
you'll take care of it.
Here.
Me?
Thank you for watching!
I'm not that you.
I think I'll have that back.
I think he's huge.
Get us the fuck out of here!
Any faster we're gonna jump off the rail!
Okay.
No!
Yeah.
Listen, there is nothing
else you could have done.
The corporations guilty here, not you.
We finally have the proof.
That way, umbrella can't get up.
I can't wait with this.
No, we can.
We can fight.
What is it?
No!
You're infected.
You will be okay.
Enough.
Who's here?
I want him in the Nemesis program.
I want her quarantine, close observation,
and a full series of blood tests.
It seems she's infected.
Take her to the raccoon city facility, and
assemble the team, the reopening the hive.
I want to know what went on down there.
Just do it.
Got it!
Yeah.
It's like a mega, a
maniac, damn on my turn.
And if you touch me, I won't rip you apart.
I'll reach it and take a bite
out of which you're gone.
I know my dear baby, I know my dear baby,
I have a seat, I've got
a reason to stop it I can't
just drop it I'm just a
better put at least I admit it
I know why
I know I know I know I know I know
Don't mean it to you, not
to, don't tell me what to do.
I am when I fucking am in your
body, change this mad place.
Oh, we've been enough to fight
something to do, you may not lie, life.
something to do, you may not lie.
Don't get it to me,
talking to me, tell you.
Don't get it to me, why do
you do the things you do?
I'm doing tests on what I do.
No, not what I want to
give on what I've got to do.
We have to realize, always been enough to
fight something that you, you may not lie.
Life, always been enough to fight
something that you, you may not lie.
Don't give it to me!
We've been enough
to fight some things I do.
We've been enough to fight
some things I do you may not like.
Don't give it to me, don't
give it to me, don't give it to me
When I get out of here,
I think I'm gonna get laid.